collegeweeklive.com 2019-09-10

# 

CollegeWeekLive, Inc. ("we" "our" or "CollegeWeekLive") takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes (i) the types of information we collect from you when you visit this website (the "Site") or use any services or content we offer (the "Services"); (ii) how we use the information we collect; (iii) with whom and why we share it; and (iv) the choices we offer regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how to contact us about our privacy practices. 

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please exit and do not use the Site. 

In plain English, here is what we affirm: 

  * You can change your registration profile at any time   
To request any of these changes, please call us at 1 (888) 697-0050 or email us at support@collegeweeklive.com
  * You can end your association with CollegeWeekLive at any time
  * CollegeWeekLive abides by all laws (such as the CAN-SPAM Act) in using your information

**1\. Information We Collect**   
In this Privacy Policy, we refer to the various types of information that you provide to us and that we collect or passively receive as the "Information."   

_Information You Provide Us_

When you register for CollegeWeekLive and at other times, you submit basic information such as your name, date of birth, gender, email address, phone number and physical address. Additionally, we may ask you to submit information related to your college plans, including without limitation, year of graduation, high school or college, major, GPA, standardized test scores and the like. Some information is mandatory to register with and use the Site; other information is optional. In addition, we may sometimes ask you to provide us with various information for other purposes, such as to enter contests or sweepstakes, or receive other products, information and features. 

**Social media information**   
We may use social media information so we can improve our member service and provide you more personalized offers and experiences. When you share social media information with us by connecting your social media account to our Site, you will be given a description of what may be collected. Each social network provides different types of information. For example, Facebook may provide your username, likes, public posts, and other basic data, while Twitter may offer your username, tweets, and basic profile. When you sign in to your account or mobile application with your social media account information, or otherwise connect to your social media account with the Services, you consent to our collection, storage, and use, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, of the information that you choose to make available to us through the social media interface. Please see your social media provider's privacy policy and help and support features for more information about how they share information when you choose to connect your account. 

**User-generated Content**   
CollegeWeekLive may offer chat features, forums and message boards. Please be advised that information posted in these venues may become public knowledge, so do not post any information that might be sensitive, and please be careful with respect to what you choose to post publicly. 

_Information Collected Passively, Through Technology_

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
We collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, when you visit our Site. The information we collect in this manner includes your IP address, browser type, operating system, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our Site (such as what pages you view, and what links you click on), and dates and times of Site visits. 

A cookie is a text file that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings in your browser. A web beacon, also known as an Internet tag or pixel tag, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Using these tools, we obtain clickstream data, which is a log of the content you visit while browsing our Site. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can often change your browser settings to prevent these cookies from collecting your personal information. Disabling cookies does not necessarily disable the use of pixel tags, web beacons and other technologies that collect information about your use of the Site. 

**Locally Stored Objects**   
The Services may employ locally stored objects ("LSOs") and other client-side storage tracking technologies in certain situations where they help to provide a better user experience, such as to remember settings, preferences, and usage similar to browser cookies, or in order to target ads, analyze ad performance, or perform user, website, or market analytics. For LSOs utilized by Adobe Flash you can access Flash management tools from [Adobe's website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html) directly. In addition, some, but not all browsers, provide the ability to remove LSOs, sometimes within cookie and privacy settings. 

**2\. Our Use of the Information**

We may use the Information you provide to us for the following purposes: 

  * Create and manage your unique user account
  * Provide services to you, including organizing and providing you with notice of online college fairs, informing you of scholarship opportunities, facilitating questions and answers regarding college admissions, financial aid and more
  * Respond to and communicate with you about your questions and comments
  * Ask you questions about our Site and our Services
  * Send you news and updates about the Site, our Services and events of interest
  * Communicate with you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, and other offers
  * Send you offers and ads for our products and services, when you browse the Site or other Sites on the Internet
  * Send you offers and ads for products and services of partner brands, or other offers we believe may be of interest to you.
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; analyzing our products; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions)
  * Perform data analyses (including market research)
  * Enforce our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.
  * We may combine the Information with other information we obtain from third parties, publicly available sources, and any other product or service we provide to further improve the relevance and effectiveness of products, services, and advertisements offered, including (but not limited to), those provided on or through the Services.

By collecting information through cookies, web beacons and other automated means, we learn how to improve and customize this Site for our visitors. We may use cookies and similar technologies to customize your visit to our Site and deliver content consistent with your interests and the manner in which you browse the Site. We may use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Site. We also may use IP addresses to help identify visitors to our Site for the duration of a session and to gather demographic information about our visitors. We may use clickstream data to determine how much time visitors spend on each web page of our Site, how visitors navigate through the Site, and how we may tailor our Site to better meet the needs of our visitors. We also use the information for compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures, including the enforcement of our Terms and Conditions. 

We may use any of the above Information in de-identified, anonymized or aggregated form for online marketing, including to show you (or help other companies to show you) display ads that may be more relevant to you. Sometimes, this involves sharing de-identified or anonymous identifiers with partners, such as advertising or other media platforms. For instance, we may use or share de-identified data you have provided to us (for instance, a unique ID) with an advertising platform to assist colleges or universities to provide you with anonymous online offers, through ads served when you browse the internet. 

**3\. Information We Share**

We may sometimes share, sell or otherwise disclose the Information we collect about you, as described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise disclosed to you when you provide us with the information, including as follows: 

  * We may share the Information with service providers who help us deliver the services you request, such as (but not limited to) hosting providers, chat room personnel and operators, credit card processors, technology and customer support services, analytics providers, market research and data management or data enhancement services. We furnish service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services.
  * We may share the Information with our corporate affiliates, advertising and marketing companies and platforms that may wish to target you with products that may be relevant to your described interests or demographic profile, and other institutions that may wish to market to you directly (such as through direct mail, display media or email channels). For instance, this may include (but is not limited to) colleges and universities you have expressed an interest in, colleges and universities that are similar to those institutions, and other marketers that sell products related to the college and university experience.
  * We may share with third parties certain anonymized or aggregated statistics about our users and their behavior while visiting our Site. We may include such data in reports made available to third parties, or to the general public. These reports will not identify individual users.
  * We may share with third party platforms and providers (such as display media platforms or other advertising services) any of the Information we receive or collect, in de-identified, anonymized or aggregated form for online marketing, including to show you (or help other companies to show you) display ads that may be more relevant to you.
  * We will disclose your personally identifiable information (or other Information) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect the rights and property of CollegeWeekLive.com, its affiliates or any other person. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose any Information to the requesting agency in doing so.
  * If we or all or substantially all of our assets, are purchased by another company (such as in a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of stock and/or assets, or other corporate change or financing transaction), the Information in our possession will likely be transferred to the successor entity. We also may share the Information during the course of any due diligence process.

**4\. Information About Other People**

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. such as your parent or guidance counselor. We may use this information to contact these people about content, opportunities and events that may be relevant to (as applicable) you or them. 

**5\. Your Data Protection Rights Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have the following data protections: 

  * If you want access to your data, or wish to correct or update your information, you can do so by emailing pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com If you would like to delete your data, please contact [pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com](mailto:pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com)
  * You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications that we send at any time. You can use the unsubscribe link located within the footer of our communications.
  * If we collected your information with consent, you can remove that consent at any time. To opt-out of other forms of communication, please contact us at [pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com](mailto:pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com)
  * You have the right to restrict the processing or request a copy of your data. To exercise this choice, you will need to contact [pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com](mailto:pqe_datacontrol@platformq.com)
  * If you created an account prior to May 25th, 2018, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

We will respond to all requests that we receive from persons wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance to data protection laws. 

**6\. Your Choices**

We may offer you certain choices in connection with the information we collect, use and share. As noted above, some information that we collect from you is required to enable you to register with and use the site. Other information is optional. Where practical, we may enable you to control the types and frequency of marketing and promotional materials you receive from us. However, unless otherwise expressly agreed, you should presume that we collect, use and share your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You may "opt out" of receiving or unsubscribe to marketing and promotional materials via email at any time by calling us at 1 (888) 697-0050, emailing us at support@collegeweeklive.com or by clicking on the Unsubscribe link in the emails we send to you and following the resulting instructions. You may "opt out" of receiving or unsubscribe to marketing and promotional materials via email at any time by calling us at 1 (888) 697-0050, emailing us at support@collegeweeklive.com or by sending a text reading "CWL STOP" to 36698. 

We also may allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks, servers and platform) to serve tailored advertising to you on the Services or on other websites or in other mobile applications, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer or other device you use to access the Services. We may also use third parties to retarget ads to you about our own Services. We neither have access to, nor does this Privacy Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed by third parties. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer or mobile browser to deliver tailored advertising (i.e., not just for the Services), you may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative's Consumer Opt-Out Link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and/or the [Digital Advertising Alliance's Consumer Opt-Out Link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertising content even if you opt-out of tailored advertising. In that case, the advertising content will just not be tailored to your interests. Also, we do not control any of the above opt-out links and are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms. 

**7\. Children Under 13**

Our Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not use our Services. If you learn of someone under 13 that has submitted personal information to us, please contact us, so that we may delete that personal information from our database. 

**8\. Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please call us at 1 (888) 697-0050 or email us at support@collegeweeklive.com 

**9\. Data Storage and Security**

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. CollegeWeekLive uses makes efforts to keep your personal information safe, as well. However, while we do take precautions against possible security breaches of our Site and your information, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will not occur. 

**10\. Changes in Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. 

**11\. Links to Other Web Sites**

The Site may, from time to time, contain links to web sites or services owned and operated by third parties ("Third Party Sites"). Those Third Party Sites are governed by terms and privacy policies of the third parties (not us). We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such Third Party Sites so that you understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on Third Party Sites. Likewise, we may provide you a way to communicate (such as by email) with third parties, such as college admissions officers. These persons are third parties, and not employed by us or subject to our policies (including this Privacy Policy) or our supervision. 

**12\. How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via the "Contact Us" page on this Site, or by writing to:   
CollegeWeekLive, Inc.   
100 Crescent Road   
Needham, MA 02494 

You may also use this address to notify us of any dispute you have with our implementation of the Privacy Policy or protection of your personally identifiable information.
